A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), Essential Office records FA1889
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), Essential Office records
1932-1999
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, David (1915-2017)
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich) (1908-1979)
Mauze, Abby Rockefeller (1903-1976)
Rockefeller, John D., Jr. (John Davison) (1874-1960)
Rockefeller, John D., III (John Davison) (1906-1978)
Rockefeller, Laurance Spelman (1910-2004)
Rockefeller, Winthrop (1912-1973)
FA1889
1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement
Original order, as received.
Scope and Contents
Documents the general workings of the office including: office manual, office procedures, employee handbooks, employee logs, directories, notices, the office letter handbook, background information on Rockefeller philanthropic organizations, and select other materials.
- Office Hours and Holidays - Policy Memoranda, 1932-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Office Manual, 1946 December 11 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- General Office Procedures - Personnel, 1954-1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Office Parties, 1946-1992 (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
- Office - Job Description, 1949 November 21 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Office - Directory, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Office - Mary Miller Memos, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- JDR and Rockefeller Family Philanthropic History, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Includes photographs and slides presentation.
- Office - Notices, 1946-1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Employee Logs, 1950-1981 (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
- Office Letter Handbook, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Background Information on Organizations, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Employee Handbooks, 1956; 1966; 1983 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Office - Directory for Cousins, 1973-1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Office - Letter to Rockefeller Family, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Office updates.
- Rockefeller Family Genealogy, 1959-1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Office - Big Apple Circus - Planning, 1986-1999 (Box 3, Folder 7)